<motd version="32" lastChanged="2024-03-15 01:15:00">Welcome to the GTA Speedrunners&apos; Server! (created and sponsored by Joshimuz, ran by 123robot and Parik)This is a revival of a community Racing/Destruction Derby/Minigame server from 2013.&#x0A;&#x0A;FOR HELP PRESS F9 to bring up the help menu, which explains all the addons.&#x0A;FPS is 30 so that physics are near identical to those in speedruns AND IT WILL NOT BE CHANGED.&#x0A;If you have a map you want added, contact 123robot. REMEMBER, always use ghost mode on, respawn time 1 second, and 1 spawn point for races unless otherwise required.&#x0A;Please use the /rate command to rate maps, low rated maps will be considered for removal.&#x0A;&#x0A; You can donate to help support the running of the server through StreamLabs (but of course only if you&apos;re able) at the following donation link: https://streamlabs.com/123robot&#x0A;&#x0A;RULES AND GUIDELINES:&#x0A;&#x0A;Basic guidelines of conduct for the server. We want to make it clear precisely what and will not be tolerated on the server.&#x0A;&#x0A;1) Don&apos;t spam the chat with lots of useless and unnecessary messages.&#x0A;2) Avoid language intended to shock, offend, or otherwise provoke, particularly hate speech and discriminatory language.&#x0A;3) Do not harass or insult other players needlessly - we want to maintain a friendly atmosphere.&#x0A;&#x0A;Consistent rule-breaking can result in anything from a mute to a total ban, so keep that in mind. Just try and act sensibly and you shouldn&apos;t have to worry about this.&#x0A;I encourage you to use the /report feature and select &apos;Player Complaints&apos; for anyone who is breaking these guidelines or causing problems.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ ?/?/2024 Update~~~&#x0A;blurb&#x0A;&#x0A;SUMMARY OF CHANGES:&#x0A;- 10 new maps&#x0A;- various maps with music have had their music disabled by default due to streamer copyright issues. You can still press M to turn the music back on.&#x0A;&#x0A;DETAILED INFORMATION:&#x0A;CHANGED MAPS:&#x0A;- [DD] &quot;Looney Toons&quot; - Music removed altogether due to the code for this map being inaccessible&#x0A;- [R] &quot;Chase The Checkpoint&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;- [R] &quot;I Know What I&apos;m Doing 1 - A Horse With No Name&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;- [R] &quot;NEOSPUGTOPIA&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;- [R] &quot;The Mines of Moria&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;- [R] &quot;What A Day At The Park&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;- [R] &quot;What A Day At The Park 2&quot; - Music muted by default&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] A Shipment for the Vagos&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Burning Vehicles Reported&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] End of Shift. Grab Pizza&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Fixed My Car&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Peren Pretzels&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Preparations for Foxtrot One&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Taking Off With The Trash&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Very Important Person&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Visit Dad&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Woozie&apos;s Jizzy Attack Failure&quot; by LotsOfS&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 15/03/2024 Update~~~&#x0A;So while the last update was, in my opinion, totally perfect - some people suggested there may have been some problems. Such as, uh, everything being broken. So we&apos;re addressing that here.&#x0A;&#x0A;- Fixed spectate mode constantly spectating nobody despite there being available players.&#x0A;- Fixed overtime not being set correctly.&#x0A;- Fixed ASS not hiding players properly on /hide 1.&#x0A;- Updated deprecated variables in the race gamemode (left over from the incredibly old versions we updated from.)&#x0A;- Fixed the Rs (respawn time) label not being set correctly.&#x0A;- Fixed maps with no descriptions saying &apos;Text&apos; on the loading screen.&#x0A;- Fixed the server failing to trigger map start events, which broke most of the things that were broken.&#x0A;- Possibly fixed the race progress bar not updating correctly? Or at least breaking less often.&#x0A;- Fixed the speedometer being missing even when enabled.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 13/03/2024 Update~~~&#x0A;Various new maps, fixes, and old stuff from two years ago being implemented.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Liberty Cheetah 01 Race&quot; by misterfolg&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Hold W Randomiser&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Mines of Moria&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] NEO SPUGTOPIA&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Paramedic&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Paramedic - San Andreas&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Shanty 8-Track Randomiser&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Shanty 8-Track Randomiser (Collisions)&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tumbleweed&quot; by Mawfeen&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Just Business&quot; for largely self-explanatory reasons.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Dubstruction Derby&quot; cause it&apos;s bad.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- New Hidden Packages region added!&#x0A;- Extra map information will now be displayed during loading screens.&#x0A;- Entering spectate mode will now spectate a random player rather than always consistently being the player in last place.&#x0A;- Various optimisations and upgrades to the race gamemode.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 10/03/2024 Update~~~&#x0A;Welcome back to the official GTA Speedrunners&apos; Server! It&apos;s back...again! Now running on a new dedicated server and sponsored by Joshimuz and his generosity, so everyone is required to worship him forever and always. Everything should be exactly how you remember it - nothing much else to say really. Revel in the nostalgia, and as always you can suggest new things in #mta-general on The123robot Discord or with the /report system. New things will be added as long as people want to develop for it, and new maps will keep being added as long as you guys keeping making them, but the server itself should keep running for a long long time to come.&#x0A;&#x0A;14 new maps have been added courtesty of misterfolg - no doubt they will all be future classics. &#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 21/03/2022 Update~~~&#x0A;Quick small update for minor additions and improvements.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 4&quot; by Ross&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Last Tug Standing&quot; by Ross&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Most Random Race of Them All&quot; cause it turned out to be a lot more boring than it sounds. I can see a version of this with more variety and less straight lines that could be interesting if someone put the work in.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- New Hidden Packages region added!&#x0A;- /votekick has been re-enabled after fixes, along with /votekill&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 15/03/2022 Update~~~&#x0A;Woah the server is back hype. After a hiatus that was supposed to be short but turned into 5 months but now it&apos;s back. At least that means the server gets extra hype, I guess :P Anyway, everything&apos;s the same as before, come to me if there are any problems, etc etc. Here&apos;s a list of new maps:&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- [R] Turismo Travel by KatastrofaS&#x0A;- [R] Going Down 3 (Freeway Intersections) by Hedning&#x0A;- [R] Taxi Drver by Jonde&#x0A;- [R] Los Santos Roofs by Ajuh&#x0A;- [R] LV Tour by Ajuh&#x0A;- [R] The Vortex Club by Jivel1&#x0A;- [R] Vance Landscaping 1 by Jivel1&#x0A;- Another collection of 40 racing maps by Waldek for you to grind, identifiable by their NC2021 prefix.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 04/03/2021 Update~~~&#x0A;Hey, so you guys have been sending in loads of maps, so even though I&apos;ve not had too much time to work on other aspects of the server, I wanted to make sure I added the new content, give you all some new stuff to enjoy!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Underwater Race&quot; by GamingMaster&#x0A;- &quot;[R] BIGHAM&quot; by The_Ghost&#x0A;- A collection of 10 racing maps by Walkek, identifiable by the NC2021-50 prefix. &#x0A;- &quot;[R] HYPERHAM&quot; by The_Ghost&#x0A;- Re-added &quot;[R] The Heist&quot; by Ali_Digitali. This is the only one of his removed maps deemed to be stable enough for re-addition. His other ones most definitely are not.&#x0A;&#x0A;Couple other minor map fixes that aren&apos;t worth mentioning, and that&apos;s literally it. But that&apos;s like, 15 new maps so, enjoy those!&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 07/02/2021 Update~~~&#x0A;First update of 2021, look at that! Mostly new maps, couple of quality of life improvements as well.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Sanchez Playground&quot; by RiDGE.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Gant And Garver&quot; by S. and Gang&#x0A;- &quot;[R] 8Lap Wallride&quot; by Ransom&#x0A;- &quot;[R] You Decide What To Drive&quot; 1, 2, and 3, a trilogy of maps by The_Ghost&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Sultans Of Swingers&quot; by Jivel1&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Streetside Flashing&quot; by Jivel1&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Rooftop Ragequit&quot; by Jivel1. This was previously on the server but removed due to a particular aspect of the map that has been changed. We&apos;ll see if people take to it more now. :P&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Racing Through The Wilderness&quot; removed due to abysmally low ratings and feedback.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- There is now a half second grace period from when everyone is spectating to the map ending, allowing players on their own to make use of the spectate respawn without instantly ending the map.&#x0A;- More Hidden Packages added in Valle Occultado, Arco Del Oeste, Easter Bay, Juniper Hill, Central and South Tierra Robada, Esplande East, Financial, and Calton Heights. To those eager hunters who found all the existing packages, get back to it! :P&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 26/12/2020 Update~~~&#x0A;So I wasn&apos;t planning on another update this soon, but there were a couple bugs that required urgent fixing. Plus I got sent in some new maps by some lovely people and I&apos;d feel bad not getting them up quick. :P So another surprise update before 2020 ends - such a surprise it even surprised me! When you think about it, this has been a pretty solid year for the server, especially considering it wasn&apos;t even running at the start of it. :D A lot of progress has been had over that time, and I&apos;m satisfied with that. But yeah, enough of that, here&apos;s the important changes:&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Pig Pen Race&quot; by choripanycristi&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Sultan Night&quot; by Ezekah&#x0A;&#x0A;BUG FIXES:&#x0A;- The race ghost will now no longer record vehicle weapon fire, so now you can no longer be murdered from the past.&#x0A;- Set as default for heli blade collisions to be disabled in all maps with ghost mode, so now strictly heli-based maps are properly playable with multiple people.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 21/12/2020 - The Christmas SR Update~~~&#x0A;Merry Christmas, everyone! Hope you&apos;re having lovely jolly holidays and all of that. In celebration of the occasion, I&apos;ve been working hard to push out a big Christmas update for you guys, and here it is! Managed to get it in before Christmas actually happened at least. Other than minor fixes, this update is just a whole load of SR maps - I remembered that this is a Speedrunner Server and decided there should be more SR-based content. :P So there&apos;s loads of that, and also another special surprise map! But yeah, this update took a lot of work from me, making sure all of the SR maps were accurate and true to their singleplayer counterparts, so don&apos;t expect another update for quite a while. But you know, you&apos;ve got like 30 new maps to grind for times on, so have fun with that. :D&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- Every single street and air race from singleplayer has been ported to the server so you can compete against each other in them live! That&apos;s 23 in total. I feel it&apos;s a bit pointless to list them all out, so you can Google a list if you don&apos;t remember them. :P Porting all of them accurately took ages by the way, so you guys better appreciate it!&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Lure&quot; ported by 123robot. Everyone&apos;s favourite mission, now playable with your friends!&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Monster&quot; ported by 123robot&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] N.O.E.&quot; ported by 123robot&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Randomizer Race 3&quot; by 123robot, the big last surprise gift! For those who aren&apos;t so interested in the serious racing and more the wacky maps, there&apos;s another one for you!&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Just Business&quot; now has respawns disabled to prevent an exploit that broke the scripting. Top times that used this have been removed.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Love A Rainy Map&quot;. Turns out no one loved it after all.&#x0A;- A duplicate of &quot;[R] Rally_Italy_SS1&quot; that had somehow been in the map pool without anyone noticing for ages. Where players have better times on the duplicate map, they have been moved to the other one.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- The F9 Help Menu now explains the race prefixes in the votemanager section. Now if anyone asks, tell them to press F9. Teach to fish!&#x0A;- Hidden Package help has been updated with the new areas containing packages.&#x0A;- New PBs are now displayed more generously, especially if fewer players are online.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 03/12/2020 Update~~~&#x0A;Don&apos;t get too excited - this isn&apos;t really a full update, more an improvement of a specific series of map. That&apos;s right, the esteemed Tug Team RacingTM series, beloved by all. Quick summary of what&apos;s changed below:&#x0A;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 2: Electric Boogaloo&quot; has been split into two maps, as the second, more challening part of the map was considered too jarring to be combined with the rest of it. The first half of the map is now &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 2: Electric Boogaloo&quot; and the challenge section of the map is now split into &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 2.5: Extra Stage&quot;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 3&quot; has been added, yet another installment in the acclaimed series. Enjoy!&#x0A;&#x0A;While this update does not include any further changes, I can assure you that more maps, fixes, and other improvements are being worked on as we speak, so more updates are to come!&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 02/12/2020 Update~~~&#x0A;In recognition of some renewed interest in the server thanks to the POWER OF LIVE STREAMS, we&apos;ve been working on several changes, improvements and fixes for the server, as well as new maps, some of which are still in the works and will come in future updates, however there&apos;s still a lot new to enjoy here. With many thanks to S. for his assistance with several of these changes:&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Going Up 2&quot; by S. &amp; Gang&#x0A;- &quot;[R] U&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Blazing Chandelle - Stage 3&quot; by Ross&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing 2: Electric Boogaloo&quot; by Ross&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Airport Construction&quot; by Gang&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Congested Slopes&quot; by Jonza&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Stunt City&quot; by R3D4NG3L&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Highway Drift&quot; by Destroyer-GT&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Ridin&apos; Around Angel Pine&quot; by Samy&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Shooting Through SF&quot; by AdnanKananda&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Vagos Drive&quot;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Fatal Freeway&quot; by KRraAaSH&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Onwards and Upwards&quot;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Precarious Pathway&quot;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Deadline&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Dinghy Race?&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Going Down 2 (Ocean Docks)&quot; by Herman-Hedning&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Going Down 5 (Easter Bay)&quot; by Herman-Hedning&#x0A;- &quot;[R] SF SPRINT&quot; by BLaCKMaMBa&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Smonster&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tank Invaded Farm&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Weapon Drop&quot; (this map is now finally playable after several attempts to add it in the past)&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Low Stakes, High Bike&quot; by Nasho&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Going Up 1&quot; has had several changes to make the race experience easier and more natural, as well as making it look a bit nicer.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Big Loop&quot; has been slightly modified to make the loop easier to complete properly.&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Musical Garages&quot; has had a bug fixed that caused the number of garages not to correctly decrease with the players.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] PingPong2.5&quot; now has the ability to respawn destroyed mines.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] HotringRaceTrack&quot; has had its repsawn time reduced.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Mountain Course&quot; now no longer allows other players to break the wooden paths you need to progress through the race.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Wu Zi Mu&quot; and &quot;[R] Farewell, My Love...&quot; are now much more accurate to their singleplayer counterparts. The sizes of checkpoints have been increased to more closely match singleplayer hitboxes, everybody now spawns where you would in singleplayer, and the ZR-350 in &quot;[R] Farewell, My Love...&quot; uses offroad wheels as in singleplayer.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Snake Farm&quot; now displays a clear warning when you are losing health from not moving.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Die Another Day&quot; uses improved text drawing code and takes away health when far away from other players as in the Infernus Showdown maps.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Liberty City Run-around&quot; now features collision over the entire city rather than only some parts, so it is now highly unlikely you will fall through somewhere you don&apos;t expect. It also now plays voice lines upon completion.&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Import/Export Race&quot; now allows you to view the full experience leaderboard as well as the shortened leaderboard with F5.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Chase the Checkpoint&quot; has less unnecessary chat output.&#x0A;The most heavily modified maps have had their ratings and times reset where the changes are too great for the stats of the original map to reflect its new state.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Hot Package: The First 2018&quot; for being broken and a bit rubbish. The general concept of a trucking race could be good with improvements in the future though.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- More hidden packages have been added to find in Tierra Robada and northern areas of San Fierro. If you had already found the existing packages, there&apos;s now more out there to discover!&#x0A;- Car colours can now generate more random values, allowing for more variety and helping your car pop out more from others.&#x0A;- Fixed the MOTD so that it displays at a smaller size for lower resolutions.&#x0A;- Obtaining a top time now informs you of your time save over your PB as well.&#x0A;- Many improvements and changes to the voting system. Maps can now be matched by their internal name so all maps can be voted for. Voting threshold for /voteredo and /votemap have been increased so that a larger majority is  required for success. /votemap [name] now sets the map being voted for as being the next map rather than instantly switching.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 03/07/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Been a little bit since the last update, eh? A lot of this stuff has been in the pipeline for a while, but now the update&apos;s finally coming to the server! This mostly focuses on general quality of life improvements and fixes to the server - not too much in the way of new maps. Still, hope you enjoy the additions! Huge thanks to Ali_Digitali, who is the main one to thank for a lot of these changes!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Snake Farm&quot; by Ali_Digitali&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Solid Poles&quot; by Gang and S.&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Tears of the Dragon&quot; now saves the longest survival times to the scoreboard.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Tower Game 1&quot; now has a map limit so that players can no longer fly endlessly out of bounds.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Hold the Line&quot; now has further improved checkpoint collisions.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] A Wise Man from the East&quot; fixes the issue that caused players to occasionally fall through the floor.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Disco Drive&quot; has decreased chances of disco cars, and added traffic lights at the beginning.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Catapult!&quot; has been modified to try to improve balance - catapults now have landing safety nets and they have a 200HP benefit.&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] NRG-500&quot; now has increased sizes for checkpoint hitboxes.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Hold the Line: Night Ring&quot; is more generally stable and uses a more dynamic colour system.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Disco Dash&quot; has more colour variation, and no more flashing buildings.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- The author of the current map is now displayed in the bottom left info panel.&#x0A;- The /2048 minigame now has a moveable window and an additional WASD control scheme.&#x0A;- Your personal best time is now displayed in the scoreboard if it&apos;s not in the top 10.&#x0A;- Top times are now outputted to the chat.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 05/05/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Happy May the 5th everyone! Here&apos;s your now monthly update, I guess - server isn&apos;t as maintenance-demanding as it was in the launch month but that doesn&apos;t mean there isn&apos;t still cool new stuff to enjoy! :D&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Noob Race&quot; by Dubgame + S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Baggy Baggage&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Cool Chainsaw&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] S.&apos; Roof Jumps&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Battle Deluxe&quot; by Ali Digitali + Mintse&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Disco Dancing&quot; by Ali Digitali + Kreedon&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Just Business&quot; by Ali Digitali&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Airport Tour&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Around SF 1&quot; and &quot;[R] Around SF 2&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Buffalo Sheriff&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Cuda&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Emperor of the Hills&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Fast Truck&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Mini LS&quot; by |CrF|Alan&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Most Random Race of Them All&quot; has had certain changes reverted that made the map more likely to generate in an unplayable state.&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Air Pain 3&quot; now reveals the location of remaining Dodo&apos;s on the map after 4 minutes instead of 5.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- Removed &quot;[MG] There Can Only Be One&quot; since it did not function as intended.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- A big new feature has been added as another way of keeping yourself occupied during maps you&apos;re not interested in playing. S. has created an add-on for coloured hidden packages that you can find and collect. Press F9 for more information on how it works and the relevant commands. At the moment, packages are only present in the north-western corner of the map, but it may be expanded in the future. Enjoy your searching!&#x0A;- Corrected how colour codes are displayed during races.&#x0A;- Added a spectate counter showing how many people are currently spectating you or someone else.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 06/04/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; It&apos;s been a while, but here&apos;s a big ol&apos; update to hopefully make up for it! This is dedicated to LotsOfS, whose birthday it is on the day of this update, so a very happy birthday to him! :D&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Going Up 1&quot; by Gang and S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Dumper Madness Reloaded&quot; by Oekeokiki and Gang&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] 555 WE Tip&quot; by S. (brand new and improved version!)&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Airpain 3&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Weird Bridge Rubbish&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Mall Rider&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Big Loop&quot; by Rickets007&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Highway Sprinting&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Inbred Escape&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Late For School&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Flash Club&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Club Club&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Baggage Race by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Cross S15&quot; by iPwn3r~ (sent in by Wuzi)&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Cross ZY&quot; by Zaya aka Zaibatsu (sent in by Wuzi)&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Farm Course&quot; by D&amp;A (sent in by Wuzi)&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Mountain Course&quot; by iPwn3r~ (sent in by Wuzi)&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Import/Export Race&quot; - Full experience leaderboard improved. Added a /showScoreBoard command.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Phase&quot; - Altered several parts of the map to be easier. Removed collision for various objects.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Sky High&quot; - Corrected respawn time&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Get Back to the Grove&quot; - increased ring sizes during Hydra section to decrease difficulty, and altered some of their placements.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Blood Harvest&quot; - Interesting concept but needs a lot of fixes&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 27/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Hi, here&apos;s a big update that hopefully won&apos;t break anything! As you can see above, due to recent incidents, I&apos;ve added basic guidelines for what is and is not considered acceptable behaviour on the server. As I say there, please /report anyone who is consistently failing to follow them. They may be edited over time so keep yourself familiar with them. Otherwise, here are the exciting changes!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;&#x0A;&quot;[R] Like a Flash&quot; by Samy&#x0A;&quot;[TW] Driving School Teamwork by S.&quot; by S.&#x0A;&#x0A;A big batch of old maps that I decided were suitable were edited and re-added:&#x0A;&#x0A;&quot;[R] BOR-KDC 040318 Buffalo&quot; by [SGA]morpp&#x0A;&quot;[R] BOR-KDC 040318 SuperGT&quot; by [SGA]morpp&#x0A;&quot;[R] BOR-KDC 040318 Turismo&quot; by [SGA]morpp&#x0A;&quot;[MG] Blood Harvest&quot; by Ali_Digitali&#x0A;&quot;[R] Hover Drop&quot; by Joshimuz&#x0A;&quot;[R] Get Back to the Grove&quot; by A_QUEEN&#x0A;&quot;[R] Sky High&quot; by Blue Zircon&#x0A;&quot;[R] Spinner Vortex&quot; by Unknown&#x0A;&quot;[R] The Most Random Race of Them All&quot; by Ali_Digitali with Edits by 123robot&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Mind the Gap&quot; - improved ending and the square circle drive.&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Musical Garages&quot; - fixed number of garages logic, fixed gettting stuck in ramps, more ramps added, monster pickup removed, music volume increased, music stopped correctly after death, fixed two people spawning in one garage, improved garage collision, added second wall for larger numbers of players, prevented the exploit that allowed you to explode the map.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] End of the Smokio&quot; - race markers rearranged, some unnecessary obstacles and spawn points removed&#x0A;- &quot;[R] GP Los Santos | GT1 | Race&quot; - increased back up to 5 laps, modified fuel consumption, improved refuelling explanation. Will see what people think of that, maybe eventually I&apos;ll finally get it right. :P&#x0A;- &quot;[TW] Verona Pier Teamwork by S.&quot; - fixed collision issues, fixed tutorial.&#x0A;- &quot;[DD] Looney Toons&quot; - added more spawns to support 64 players&#x0A;- &quot;[R] PingPong2.5&quot; - added more mines to hopefully prevent the issue where they all break.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;&#x0A;- Vehicle respawning improved to save your nitro and nitro level.&#x0A;- Bottom right corner text improved to be more visible.&#x0A;- Improved the &quot;Reports&quot; system (which was previously there, just not advertised). You should use that to report players, broken maps or features, or to give new feature ideas.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 23/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Welcome to another fairly minor update yeah!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Emergency Landing&quot; by S. (re-added after fixes)&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Blazing Chandelle - Stage 2&quot; by Ross&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Tug Team Racing&quot; by Ross&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- Added explanation of the fuel system to &quot;[R] GP Los Santos | GT1 | Race&quot;&#x0A;- Minor changes to &quot;[R] L.S. Noire&quot;&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- Further improvements to the antiBlow script.&#x0A;&#x0A;There are lots more maps being worked on in the background by various people, so anticipate some cool new maps fairly soon!&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 21/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Hello, welcome to another update. I&apos;m sure a million broken things will immediately be found but please remember we also fixed a bunch of other things too and didn&apos;t just make an update to break everything for you. Also special thanks to Jivel1 and SpeedyFolf for helping test this update - they were a great help!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] GP Los Santos | GT1 | Race&quot; by Vally with edits by Wuzi, 123robot, and S.&#x0A;- &quot;[R] L.S. Noire&quot; by Hoxi&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Farewell, My Love...&quot; by Talidan&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Real Driving School&quot; is now named &quot;[SR] City Slicking&quot;&#x0A;- Even more fixes to &quot;[TW] Verona Pier Teamwork by S.&quot;&#x0A;- Fixed several maps that were improperly set to development mode.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Los Bullet&quot;&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Emergency Landing&quot; - Will be re-added once fixes are implemented.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- Fixed the broken race timer.&#x0A;- Fixes to the FPS and Ping display.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 19/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A;Another update because people are doing too many cool fixes and making too many cool maps. How dare you guys make things!&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Blazing Chandelle - Stage 1&quot; by Ross&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Faggio Fierro&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] The Green Sabre&quot; by Yumitsu&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Blista Club&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[SR] Los Sepulcros&quot; by Hoxi&#x0A;- &quot;[R] The Slamvan Club&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Shades Only BabyRage&quot; by Terrtail&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Emergency Landing&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;[MG] Musical Garages&quot; by Mowemax&#x0A;- &quot;[R] Easier NRG Map&quot; by Terrtail (replacing Easy NRG Map)&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- &quot;Verona Pier Teamwork (BY S. BY THE WAY)&quot; has had several fixes and improvements that are too much to list  herebut I assure you they&apos;re all good.&#x0A;- &quot;There Can Be Only One&quot; has been improved so it hopefully works properly now. Big emphasis on hopefully.&#x0A;- &quot;Hot Package: The First 2018&quot; has been changed to fix the bug where it respawns you in spectate.&#x0A;- &quot;Infernus Showdown: SF Airport&quot; has removed the exploit where you could hide on the docks.&#x0A;- &quot;Tears of the Dragon&quot; has been changed to fix the bug where you get set on fire forever.&#x0A;- &quot;Randomizer Oval Race&quot; has fixed you occasionally spawning in the floor.&#x0A;- &quot;Hard With Style&quot; now uses Ghost Mode. BY THE WAY USE GHOST MODE IN YOUR MAPS.&#x0A;- Corrected the categorisation for some maps.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;Weapon Drop&quot; because IT REFUSES TO WORK.&#x0A;- &quot;Rooftop Ragequit&quot; until an improved version is prepared.&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- AFK script received several improvements. Now it works properly, and flashes big text in your face so you can&apos;t miss it. :P&#x0A;- Anti-Blow script to try and help prevent chain explosions.&#x0A;- Added various extra details in the bottom left corner (ping, FPS, map).&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 16/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Another big update! Wow woah magical.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;Catalina Quadrilogy&quot; by Lordmau5&#x0A;- &quot;There Can Only Be One&quot; by Joshimuz&#x0A;- &quot;Import/Export Race&quot; by S.&#x0A;- &quot;Hard with Style&quot; by Mateoryt&#x0A;- &quot;Heinz Faust Racing&quot; by S. (re-added with major improvements)&#x0A;- &quot;Racing With The Supastuka&quot; by S.&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- All maps based on in-game speedrun routes now have their own prefix - [SR]. This helps distinguish them from ordinary races for people who prefer one or the other, and also removes the need to figure out the exact speedrun category of a map.&#x0A;- Robbing Uncle Sam and Weapon Drop should finally work properly now. If they don&apos;t I&apos;ll be very upset.&#x0A;- Car Game DD now ends with a hunter instead of a Rhino. Also fixed issues with fake blips.&#x0A;- Liberty City Run-Around has been updated to use more accurate collisions. Some checkpoints have also been modified and a kill plane was added under the city.&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;555 We Refuse to Reset&quot;  &quot;Badlands (mission)&quot; (more inaccurate speedrun-type maps that need improving)&#x0A;- &quot;Newton&apos;s Cradle&quot;&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- Finally added an auto-AFK system! Anyone AFK for about 15 seconds or longer will now automatically go into spectate mode.&#x0A;- Additionally, players in spectate mode will now no longer hold up the map vote.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 14/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; This update is mostly concentrated on fixing stuff, mostly in maps but also some resources. You could also say this MOTD itself is updated because now it&apos;s a proper changelog. Ooh fancy.&#x0A;&#x0A;NEW MAPS:&#x0A;- &quot;Haytona Endurance&quot;  &quot;Haytona Hotring&quot; by Uguu (these two maps replace the original Haytona)&#x0A;- &quot;Porsche Cup&quot; by Trevortjes&#x0A;- &quot;Any% - Robbing Uncle Sam&quot; by yumitsu&#x0A;- &quot;Disco Derby 3D&quot; by Ali_Digitali (technically not new but re-added to map pool after fixes)&#x0A;&#x0A;MAP EDITS:&#x0A;- All maps with overly long respawn times have now been reduced to 1 second respawn!&#x0A;- Infernus Showdowns (health drains when far from players, text rendering improved)&#x0A;- Pirates of San Andreas (uses big red text like Infernus Showdowns)&#x0A;- Hold the Line (marker placements improved, respawn velocity fixed)&#x0A;- 3-Bit-Hit: Desert (removed SF spawn)&#x0A;- Hotring Race Track (removed unnecessary extra laps)&#x0A;- Top of the Pyramid (now version 3, hopefully it&apos;s a bit better)&#x0A;- Move! (collisions disabled)&#x0A;- Weapon Drop (support for 64 players)&#x0A;- Gravitron (collisions disabled)&#x0A;&#x0A;REMOVED MAPS:&#x0A;- Reset Opportunity (someone will make a better one hopefully)&#x0A;- Heinz Faust Racing (may return later with improvements)&#x0A;&#x0A;RESOURCES:&#x0A;- Fixes to ASS&#x0A;- Updates to Race Progress bar&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~12/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Big update wow! Four brand new server resources have been added - an improved Anti-Social Simulator, a GUI minigame (use /2048), private messages, and time played on the scoreboard. Updated the help manager. Added new maps from S., Uguu, Joshimuz, and WordOfWind. Removed some maps that didn&apos;t work or were breaking the server (LOOKING AT YOU ALI). Updated some maps with improvements.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~10/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Added 3 new maps provided by WordofWind, Terrtail, and Yoka. Sort of balancing that out is the removal of 3 maps that were causing server issues or need updating. A couple other maps were also updated for fixes.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~05/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Map pool increased to 224 with the re-addition of all the old maps Joshimuz found plus 4 brand new ones by LateLJ, Trevortjes, and Jivel1. Also updated 5 existing maps.&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 01/03/2020 Update~~~&#x0A; Server is back (again!) under new management! It is now being hosted by 123robot and should be in no danger of going down for the foreseeable future, even if nobody plays on it. :P Him and Parik will be mainly responsible for maintaining it, so probably bug them if you have issues instead of Joshimuz, as he is a very important speedrunner man with no time for silly MTA servers! Other than that, almost everything should be how you remember it if you played it before, so enjoy!&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 03/04/2018 Update ~~~&#x0A;Map pool increased to 162, removed 5 more low rated maps: The-True-Olympic-Jump (3.07), Sky High (3.81), Spinner Vortex (3.97), CraRyzaze (4.43) and Hover Drop (4.71).&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 11/03/2018 Update ~~~&#x0A;Map pool increased to 158, removed 5 more low rated maps: CW-BOR-KDC-040318-Turismo (1.8), CW-BOR-KDC-040318-SuperGT (2.67), Blood Harvest (2.8), CW-BOR-KDC-040318-Buffalo (3.44), Randomizer (the &quot;fake&quot; one, 4.65).&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 05/03/2018 Update ~~~&#x0A;We had 105 maps, and 100 maps seems like a decent amount so I removed 5 low rated maps: Airport and Back (2.3), Get Back to The Grove (3.2), HydraEscape (3.5), Monster Madness (3.6) and Beverly&apos;s Funneral (4.5)&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 13/02/2018 Update ~~~&#x0A;Since the 6 days the server has been up again a lot of new (and old) maps have been added. Also there is a brand new voting system. I&apos;m working on adding a carhide script (all the pre-existing ones will break non-ghostmode maps and the DDs and are not open source so I can&apos;t fix them) however this will probably have to wait until after ESA (I&apos;m gone from 17-25).&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 07/02/2018 Update ~~~&#x0A;Wow, that was a long hiatus. After over 4 years this server makes it&apos;s glorious return. I&apos;m currently testing this to see if people are interested again (aka server isn&apos;t only used when I stream it).&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 15/12/2013 Update ~~~&#x0A;Remember to use /rate to rate good and bad maps, bad maps will be removed every now and then to keep a good standard of map pool. &quot;/rate 7&quot; means to give a map a 7 out of 10 rating.&#x0A;Press F9 for help using the server&apos;s modes and mods.&#x0A;If you would like your map added to the server, send Joshimuz a PM on twitch.tv &#x0A;A proper way of sending in maps will be made Soon(TM)&#x0A;&#x0A;~~~ 14/12/2013 Update ~~~&#x0A;The play again option in the vote-manager is now limited to 2 times, meaning a map can now only be played 3 times maximum, before playing another map.&#x0A;The amount of choices was also reduced to 5 maps and play again.&#x0A;These changes are to promote playing of other maps, instead of the 6+1 Towers-&gt; Kappa Towers-&gt; Disco Derby -&gt; 6+1 Towers endless cycle that was happening.</motd>
